<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>summary_of_BLF_from_rincondebetty_ on 昨天</title>
    <link>https://xrspook.github.io/tags/summary_of_blf_from_rincondebetty_/</link>
    <description>Recent content in summary_of_BLF_from_rincondebetty_ on 昨天</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <copyright>xrspook</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2004 02:52:30 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xrspook.github.io/tags/summary_of_blf_from_rincondebetty_/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2002-rincondebetty</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1088707950/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2004 02:52:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1088707950/</guid>
      <description>由于我收集的rincondebetty summary太新，以至有一些剧情没有了，难怪我看的rincondebetty summary和八月4翻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>说明（summary of Yo soy Betty la Fea from rincondebetty）</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087537970/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2004 13:52:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087537970/</guid>
      <description>Summary 2-4是Ecomoda的危机，抵押公司等事情，Armando很信任Betty，把Ecomoda全部转成Betty名下公司的抵押，以获得银行</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 18</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087100176/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2004 12:16:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087100176/</guid>
      <description>SUMMARY 18 The cuartel leaves Betty’s office when Marcela enters it, thinking that Marcela is there to ask Betty to give the office to her brother Daniel. They start praying to all the saints they know in the hopes of being under their protection (funny). Betty tells Marcela that she will have the report ready in 10 minutes. Marcela: I didn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 17</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087100112/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2004 12:15:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087100112/</guid>
      <description>SUMMARY 17 Betty is talking to Dona Catalina and asks her if she called Michel to come to her rescue. Betty tells her she’s made her decision and that she wants to leave EcoModa as soon as possible. Betty informs Cata that Armando broke up with Marcela because he is probably interested in Alejandra and she can’t bear to see him with</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 16</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087013661/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2004 12:14:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087013661/</guid>
      <description>SUMMARY 16 At the event Betty and Cata talk: Betty: Doña Catalina, I ‘m confused, he’s very different, he’s changed a lot, he’s treating me too good, I don’t understand.Cata: But he had promised to change and it seems that he did or no?Betty: Yes, he’s definitely changed a lot,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 15</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087013550/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2004 12:12:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087013550/</guid>
      <description>SUMMARY 15 ECOMODA RECEPTION AREA 2nd FLOOR Wearing a dark suit, white shirt and a light yellow tie, a Very Handsome Armando Mendoza, has just returned from his trip. He is standing in the middle of the reception area and reading a sheet of paper he had pulled from his briefcase. As he reads, he shows a little smile on his face. (Aura Maria makes signals with her hands to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 14</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087013500/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2004 12:11:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087013500/</guid>
      <description>SUMMARY 14 PRESIDENCIA EARLY EVENING Betty is sitting at her desk in deep thoughts while Miguel (the computer technician) installs her computer. When he finishes, he tells her so, but she is so deep in her thoughts that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t hear him. Miguel taps her shoulder and tells her that he has finished. Betty thanks him and stares ahead again as he looks at her. Betty noticing thanks him again</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 13</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087013481/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2004 12:11:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087013481/</guid>
      <description>Summary 13 BETTY&amp;rsquo;S HOUSEIt is morning and Betty and Nicolas are getting ready for their first day of work. Nicolas asks Betty to tell him if he&amp;rsquo;s dressed like a Vice President, and Betty smiling replies by asking him if what he wants to know is whether he looks good for la peliteñida, then the answer is yes, he looks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 12</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086927003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2004 12:10:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086927003/</guid>
      <description>Summary 12 CARTAGENA A plaza in Cartagena, filled with umbrella covered cafe tables. Betty wearing a summer white blouse and light blue skirt, walks among the people (as she is going to meet Michel). Two young men pass next to her and one of them gives her a compliment. She looks back and realizes it is she he is talking to. She quickly walks away from them, but stops to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 11</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086926999/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2004 12:09:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086926999/</guid>
      <description>Summary 11 CARTAGENA - A PARKING LOT BY THE SEA Cata finds Betty, and tells her that she has to go to a cocktail to begin some arrangements for a video, so Betty is to take the beauty queens to the hotel, so that they can be ready by seven thirty. Betty is shocked! Me? Cata notices the uncertainty in Betty&amp;rsquo;s face and tells her &amp;ldquo;How embarrassing Betty, I know</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 10</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086926928/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2004 12:08:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086926928/</guid>
      <description>Summary 10 Daniel steps out of the elevator, walks over to Patricia and asks if she has a photograph of herself, a full view. He has a couple of friends that he would like for them to view it. He believes that this would be better than him describing her. He states that after they see her picture there will be no more words needed and she will be kept</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 9</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086926856/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2004 12:07:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086926856/</guid>
      <description>Summary 9 AT THE OFFICE Due to Sandra&amp;rsquo;s crying, Mariana puts out a 911 call to Betty. Sandra notices Mario approaching and quickly gets up out of her chair and acts as though she is looking for something on Mariana desks. Mario notices that she has been crying and inquiries to the reason. Sandra informs him that she is ill with the flu. This answer seems to satifsy Mario as</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 8</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086840360/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2004 12:06:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086840360/</guid>
      <description>Summary 8 Betty’s Bedroom Nicolas, (sits by Betty and puts his arms around her) asks her why she didn’t notice that they were playing. Betty answers that when a person is in love they do not see reality. He tells her that he is not the most appropriate person to be speaking about love, but he would like to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 7</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086840277/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2004 12:04:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086840277/</guid>
      <description>Summary 7 Betty tells Armando that she agrees to fake the numbers once again on the report for the September board meeting and asks if she can leave for lunch. After she leaves, Mario comments that it’s a good thing Armando makes Betty happy because that way everyone can be happy. Armando just rolls his eyes in response. As Mariana and Sandra listen on in the background,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 6</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086840271/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2004 12:04:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086840271/</guid>
      <description>Summary 6 Hugo tells Patricia that he already knows who Delmira Agustini is. Though Patricia whines for some gossip, Hugo says that he will only tell Marcela directly because she’s the only interested party. Marcela walks into Betty’s office and asks her to check if the money from the sales has come in so they can make payroll. Betty stares</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 5</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086840130/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2004 12:02:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086840130/</guid>
      <description>Summary 5 Mario enters Armando’s office and Betty looks nervously at him. Armando directs her to get ready and she goes to tell the cuartel that she’s going home later. Mario asks Armando if he heard right: is all set up? Yes, Armando replies soberly and pulls out a bottle. No, no, says Mario, stopping him, Yo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 4</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086753678/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2004 12:01:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086753678/</guid>
      <description>Summary 4 Freddy is speaking to the hotel employee and informing him that Jenny is a model and that they are waiting for him. The employee shows them in as the Cuartel watches. Betty is concerned that involving Armando could cause him big problems with Marcela. Sandra tells her to stop worrying. She tells her that they will be grateful to them for unmasking Patricia. Sophia, angry that Jenny has</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 3</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086753583/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2004 11:59:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086753583/</guid>
      <description>Summary 3 Hugo and the models are rehearsing for the fashion show while the board members watch. Claudia Bosch winks at Armando and Marcela notices. Patricia, who is sitting next to Marcela, is there to regale her with the story about Armando talking to Claudia prior to the rehearsal. Marcela asks Patricia for the name of the model who is being so friendly with Armando. After the rehearsal, Margarita and</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 2</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086753579/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2004 11:59:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086753579/</guid>
      <description>Summary 2 Sánchez tells Nicolás that they have to acount for all of EcoModa&amp;rsquo;s property prior to placing the lien. Bertha tells Sofía that she has figured out how to get Patricia to undergo a pregnancy test and finally figure out if she&amp;rsquo;s faking or not. The banks start calling EcoModa since the Chamber</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary 1</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086753154/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2004 11:52:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1086753154/</guid>
      <description>Summary 1 Once upon a time&amp;hellip; The perspective of the first few scenes is Betty’s. We don’t see her, but see the world’s reaction to her. She arrives at EcoModa for her job interview. First she runs into Wilson and tells him that she has a job interview. She then meets Aura M</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>