<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>summary_of_EcoModa_from_rincondebetty_ on 昨天</title>
    <link>https://xrspook.github.io/tags/summary_of_ecomoda_from_rincondebetty_/</link>
    <description>Recent content in summary_of_EcoModa_from_rincondebetty_ on 昨天</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <copyright>xrspook</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2004 13:29:39 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xrspook.github.io/tags/summary_of_ecomoda_from_rincondebetty_/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 26</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087536579/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2004 13:29:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087536579/</guid>
      <description>Episode 26 Merci: I loved the final episode! It was interesting, moving, comical, romantic, and very sweet. For the Spaniards who are anti-Jarmandistas - I believe this episode completely vindicates Dr Mendoza in spades&amp;hellip; As Betty used to say during the good ol&amp;rsquo; days, &amp;ldquo;So divine!&amp;rdquo; All the actors shone&amp;hellip; I am a bit sentimental, so one tear after another welled up, knowing that this was good-bye. I hope when</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 25</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087536538/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2004 13:28:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087536538/</guid>
      <description>Episode 25 Freddy and Aura María walk up the church&amp;rsquo;s red carpet (hastily unrolled by Freddy) as Freddy vaguely hums the Wedding March under his breath, greets his aunt and uncle, and thinks to himself with a little bit of panic that this really is goodbye to his life as a bachelor. The priest starts the ceremony, but interrupts it to complain about Freddy&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;gringo&amp;rdquo; name</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 24</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087536504/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2004 13:28:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087536504/</guid>
      <description>Episode 24 Beth: i finally started to get curious about the prices mentioned in the course of these shows -especially since several feature in this episode. so i looked up the exchange rate. as of the day i originally did this summary (20 May 2002), the rate was approximately 2,357 Colombian pesos to one US dollar; so from there on, whenever prices are mentioned, i have included the approximate amount</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 23</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087536129/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2004 13:22:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087536129/</guid>
      <description>Episode 23 Merci: The leitmotif of the episode were the nearly-operatic scolds which Armando directed towards Freddy. Throughout the episode, Freddy was distracted by his little worry that Aura María might slip through his fingers and that Kenneth would continue his [Kenneth&amp;rsquo;s] pursuit of his [Freddy&amp;rsquo;s] &amp;ldquo;grillita&amp;rdquo; (little cricket), &amp;ldquo;reinita&amp;rdquo; (little queen), etc. etc&amp;hellip; Beth: if you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of Freddy, you will probably love this</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 21</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449663/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 13:21:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449663/</guid>
      <description>Episode 21 Armando is in his bathroom at home, looking at the bruises left by the blows from Calderón and the bite mark given to him by the witch, skinny Andrea&amp;hellip; He is putting on a [i think] white bathrobe and has a look on his face like he can&amp;rsquo;t believe the kind of mess he&amp;rsquo;s gotten himself into&amp;hellip; Betty arrives to tend</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 20</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449599/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 13:19:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449599/</guid>
      <description>Episode 20 Merci: What can you say about the little group of male executives at EcoModa and Freddy? They&amp;rsquo;re all a bunch of idiots!! Poor guys, they share but two neurons between the lot of them&amp;hellip; Beth: as i did with a number of the summaries, the original translation of this was done a bit at a time. however, instead of being sent out a day apart, this time there</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 22</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449527/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 13:18:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449527/</guid>
      <description>Episode 22 Merci: Tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode was terrific! Who knew Dr Armando Mendoza Sáenz could play a guitar? And what&amp;rsquo;s more, that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t sing as badly as that night he and Betty &amp;ldquo;sang?&amp;rdquo; Today I really did cry with laughter&amp;hellip; Hopefully the summary will give you an idea of just how delightful this episode was&amp;hellip; The episode starts where we left off last week: Maruja saying</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 18</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449484/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 13:18:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449484/</guid>
      <description>Episode 18 Merci: I cried with laughter watching today&amp;rsquo;s episode! Poor Armando - no matter how hard he tries, he still can&amp;rsquo;t manage to make Calderón act like an adult&amp;hellip; The elevator doors to the Mendoza-Pinzón family apartment open and we see Don Hermes and Doña Julia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 19</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449456/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 13:17:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449456/</guid>
      <description>Episode 19 Beth: Merci, who as you all know writes the Spanish summaries i use for these translations, seems to have taken a break from summarizing for this episode. so instead of Merci&amp;rsquo;s summary, we have a &amp;ldquo;Valeriana&amp;rdquo; from Delta, one of the forum members. in point of fact, what follows is actually considerably more than a true Valeriana as i have come to understand the term, since altho it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 17</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449166/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 13:12:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087449166/</guid>
      <description>Episode 17 Merci: EcoModa continues to be fantastic! Today was extremely funny. After Betty and Armando my favorite couple has to be: Mario and Armando! Incredibly, THREE days passed in one single episode&amp;hellip; What continues to be terrible are the vaunted &amp;ldquo;advances&amp;rdquo; (teasers for the next episode) - they have NOTHING to do with the actual story. Today there weren&amp;rsquo;t any teasers since I believe there won&amp;rsquo;t be a show</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 16</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362693/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2004 13:11:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362693/</guid>
      <description>Episode 16 Merci: This program gets BETTER every day! Last night&amp;rsquo;s episode was fantastic&amp;hellip; We see Betty and Armando walking along a street in Bogotá - Armando carrying two packages and Betty pushing Camila&amp;rsquo;s stroller. Armando turns to look at a very attractive woman; the woman looks back at him and recognizes him. She greets him very affectionately - she&amp;rsquo;s a model who has a</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 15</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362564/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2004 13:09:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362564/</guid>
      <description>Episode 15 I am here drinking a blackberry juice while I write this summary of Ecomoda&amp;rsquo;s episode #15. And what an episode!! It was fantastic, marvelous, ingenious, etc, etc. Nor can I fail to mention that Doctor Armando Mendoza is more adorable than ever&amp;hellip; The scenes they cut out explain very clearly why Gabriela acted so strangely when she saw Armando arrive in Ecomoda in the morning&amp;hellip; And also Armando</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 14</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362548/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2004 13:09:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362548/</guid>
      <description>Episode 14 Betty&amp;rsquo;s in Armando&amp;rsquo;s office, talking on the phone. She tells the person on the other end of the line that she is waiting to hear from her parents before heading out for the dinner at her aunts&amp;rsquo; house&amp;hellip; Armando is in the men&amp;rsquo;s room, but when he returns -Betty says to the person on the phone- they are going to continue looking at the at the Oracle of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362433/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2004 13:07:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362433/</guid>
      <description>Episode 13 The episode began as it ended last week&amp;hellip; Gutiérrez summons Natasha for an interview, Wilson finds the &amp;ldquo;lost&amp;rdquo; purse, and Don Hermes heads off to find Jenny in Hugo&amp;rsquo;s workshop. Jenny tries to smother Don Hermes in hugs while he asks that she calm herself. She tells him that she left Efraín because she was</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 12</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362380/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2004 13:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362380/</guid>
      <description>Episode 12 Merci: Our beloved and adored Dr. Mendoza behaved very, very badly today&amp;hellip; But Doña Betty will put him in his place!! Beth: WARNING: in addition to Merci&amp;rsquo;s comments, this translation contains even more asides from me than usual, some of them rather long. i don&amp;rsquo;t think it will come as any surprise to you all that i think quality-wise there is no comparison between the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 11</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362307/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2004 13:05:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087362307/</guid>
      <description>Episode 11 Our beloved and adored Dr. Armando Mendoza emerges from the elevator in search of the bag with the things from his car - before Betty sees it. Mariana tells him it&amp;rsquo;s in Betty&amp;rsquo;s office, so he asks her where Betty is. She tells him Betty&amp;rsquo;s with Kenneth at the plant. Armando -poor guy, the handsomest fool to the Nth degree- asks if Betty took the things from the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 10</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087275870/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2004 13:04:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087275870/</guid>
      <description>Episode 10 In Armando and Betty&amp;rsquo;s apartment building&amp;hellip; Betty goes down to the garage looking for Armando so they can go to work. Armando, who has hastily hidden Suji in the trash room, rushes over to Betty and asks her what she&amp;rsquo;s doing there. She asks what he &amp;rsquo;s doing and he tells her he was throwing away some trash he found in the car&amp;hellip; Armando tells Betty to wait</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087275821/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2004 13:03:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087275821/</guid>
      <description>Episode 9 In the restaurant&amp;hellip; Mario tells Armando that the party needs to continue, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter that he and Suji (or whatever her name is) have to go. Armando doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to give his car keys to Mario, so Mario promptly sits back down with his girlfriend and they start to kiss again. This makes Armando and Gabriela really uncomfortable, so Armando gives his keys to Mario. Gabriela wants</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 8</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087275793/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2004 13:03:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087275793/</guid>
      <description>Episode 8 The deal with Fashion Group Betty, Armando, Mario, Kenneth, and Gabriela are all meeting in the conference room to finalize the details of the deal with Fashion Group. Everyone agrees that the deal is a fantastic idea&amp;hellip; Gabriela explains that she and Kenneth will be in charge of all the production for the American market and ask the EcoModa group to facilitate things for them by providing offices,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 7</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087275666/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2004 13:01:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087275666/</guid>
      <description>Episode 7 The episode starts with the last scene from last week, when EcoModa and Fashion Group reach an agreement to work together and decide to meet later that day to finalize everything. Outside the conference room we see the Cartel and Freddy. Freddy is chatting with Inesita, telling her he&amp;rsquo;s worried about the presence of the gringo at EcoModa. Inesita berates him for not getting serious and proposing to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087189166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2004 12:59:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087189166/</guid>
      <description>Episode 6 Gabriela cannot believe what Kenneth tells her about his dinner with Aura María, the deception by the EcoModa employees, and the mess they created. She is very angry and tells Kenneth they&amp;rsquo;ll be leaving for Miami first thing. At Aura María&amp;rsquo;s house, we see Freddy bringing her a cup of coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 5</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087189121/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2004 12:58:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087189121/</guid>
      <description>Episode 5 Sofía asks to speak with Betty before she leaves. Betty asks Armando to leave her alone with the Cuartel and he leaves [Merci: poor guy, they&amp;rsquo;ve got him so well-trained&amp;hellip; Beth: note, the word used means &amp;ldquo;well-trained&amp;rdquo; in the sense of a performing animal or such]. The Cuartel, their tails between their legs, tells Betty they aren&amp;rsquo;t coming to ask for her help but</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 4</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087188972/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2004 12:56:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087188972/</guid>
      <description>Episode 4 We start the episode where we left off last week: Freddy taking Gabriela and Kenneth on a tour of Production and the President&amp;rsquo;s office while Armando, Betty, Nicolás and Gutiérrez arrive at the company and get onto the elevator. Freddy takes his guests to the showroom and asks &amp;ldquo;Doctora Valdé</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087188889/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2004 12:54:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087188889/</guid>
      <description>Episode 3 Merci: I get tired of the Cartel sometimes, but I have to admit I laughed out loud during tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode of EcoModa&amp;hellip; The episode started as it ended last week, with Armando and Betty in their bedroom watching the Bogotá Fashion show, and Betty saying that she agrees to talking to the people recommended by Calderón</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087102368/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2004 12:52:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087102368/</guid>
      <description>Episode 1 The first episode begins at Armando and Betty&amp;rsquo;s (their &amp;ldquo;casita&amp;rdquo;) is a beautiful two-story condo - very, very nice in my opinion. We see a ball bouncing down the stairs and hear Armando talking to his daughter. Then we see Armando, who is wearing a birthday hat and blowing on a noisemaker. It looks like it&amp;rsquo;s the baby&amp;rsquo;s birthday. Betty meets them at the bottom of the stairs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2</title>
      <link>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087102363/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2004 12:52:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrspook.github.io/post/1087102363/</guid>
      <description>Episode 2 Armando: Betty, my love, look - I think we need to talk about this, we need to clarify this or something - you know? Betty: Everything&amp;rsquo;s already very clear for me. And don&amp;rsquo;t even bother trying to tell me this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to do with a woman. Armando: Well, yes, it does have to do with a woman. And that&amp;rsquo;s precisely what we need to talk about. Betty:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>